The Portuguese named
this city Bom Bahia...
... and gave it as a wedding
gift to the British.
It wasn't their father's property.
And the British changed
its name to Bombay.
Drive faster.
But now enough.
This city won't be known by a name...
... given by the British!
This city belongs
to our Goddess Mumba Devi.
She's our mother.
This city will no longer
be known as Bombay...
... but as Mumbai!
What will it be called?
Mumbai!
- What will it be called?
- Mumbai!
What will this city be called?
Mumbai!
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, sir.
Turn the car around.
Quickly.
Turn it around.
Don't mess with my family.
Turn the car around.
Take a left.
If you mess with a Marathi,
He will hit back.
If anyone dares to take your rights...
... he'll be lying on the
streets covered in his own blood.
I have warned the government...
If you have your guy in Dubai
... I have mine in Dadar..
Stay in line.
Boss.
Let me get into the VIP line please.
It's not for you... for VIPs only.
- A line won't define my status.
- I see...
When you have status
you don't stand in lines.
Stay in your line.
Ok my lord, prayers from here only for today.
Pay up. Pay up. Come on pay up...
Where's the protection money?
Pay up. Pay up.
Come on. Come on.
Cash only. Cash only.
Where's your protection money?
Come on, hurry up, hurry up.
But I paid two days ago.
Rascal!
You paid two days ago, huh!
What is all this?
What is it?
Ours is a partnership,
and this is our share of profits.
All these shops are
Gaitonde's property.
Look at me.
Our job is
to collect his share...
... your job is to pay
with no questions asked.
Understood.
Come on.
It's become a routine with them.
They come,
they scare, they take our money.
Nonsense...
This is not acceptable.
It is...
It has always been,
and always will be.
If not Gaitonde,
there will be some Shinde or a Lande.
- This will continue.
- You're absolutely right, father.
Someone's always going to be there.
Yes someone will always be around,
but it won't be you.
The local boys have no
guts to stand up to anyone.
Do you seriously think
I'll get all wired up with your speech...
... and go beat them up.
Stop your drama and go to college.
No one's going to get
into a fight for your sake.
I can see that.
See what?
How you waste your days at the gym
evenings with volleyball,
and nights with carrom.
Your entire life revolves around it.
And you're busy building hospitals,
aren't you?
Someday I will.
Do come if you need treatment...
... only if your
blood starts to boil.
Come, I'll drop you to school.
If we wait here any longer,
she'll make my life hell.
Come on.
Bye.
One bread-butter and tea.
Careful.
What a guy...
Are you playing on our team or theirs?
- I missed...
- Balls you missed.
Out with the truth now.
How many cream rolls
did he offer you?
Speak up. Come on.
Leave it,
he's always going to be a loser.
I'll show you someday...
A man should have nerves of steel...
... even cats have long whiskers.
Where's the protection money?
- How old are you?
- Thirty-two.
- And I am twelve.
- Quite the grown-up.
Not yet, I am not.
But in a couple of years I'll
be 20, and you'll be 40.
I'll be bigger and stronger...
... but you won't be.
If we meet again,
then what will you do?
What will I do?
Amartya.
Gaitonde's men are beating up Arjun.
Arjun!
Amar. I've brought dinner.
Sit.
I stay quiet for his sake.
Even my blood boils...
Even I get furious...
But I stay quiet for his sake.
Because if anything happens to me...
... there will be no
one to look after him.
I know.
We all know.
And if anything had happened to him...
... then no one could've controlled me.
Hey.
How is your brother?
Tell that rug rat
not to be a wise-guy.
You managed to save
his life yesterday.
But the next time I'll
chop his head off and throw him down.
Now pay up.
Whoever pays them...
... will lose his arm next!
No more protection money!
Rascal!
Who chopped off Potya's hand?
He's a local kid, sir.
His name is Amartya.
What hole were you in
when he was chopping his hand?
I... that...
That?
Do you have that?
Then why were you
watching like a coward?
You get paid by the government
and me too...
... but work for neither.
What's your job?
What is your job?
To look the other way.
When?
When my boys are bashing someone up.
Not when my guys
are getting bashed up.
Understood.
I want to see that guy in here before 5pm.
Otherwise, I'll make you wipe
Potya's ass for the rest of your life!
Understand?
What are you still sitting here for?
Get up. Go...
Enjoying a meal here.
- Shengya...
- Yes, boss.
Send that builder in.
- Chopped off his hand.
- Totally.
And beat everyone up.
Left, right, and centre.
Shut up!
It's all your fault.
Why did you have to argue with them?
Huh...
I never said a word for your sake.
And you want to be a hero.
Amartya.
Your time's come.
Come, the boss is calling you.
I've a question, Mastekar.
You don't have a tail...
... then what do you
wag in front of Gaitonde?
Take him in!
No one touches me.
I'll come myself.
Look after him.
Take him away.
Let's go.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Did you chop Potya's hand?
He lay a hand on my brother.
And anyway, I did him
a favor by chopping his hand.
He can't take protection
money anymore...
... but at least he can beg.
After I am through with you,
you won't even be able to beg.
Take a look.
Take one good last look at
the setting sun.
Because it won't rise for you again.
Have you ever heard about
the night not letting the sun rise.
Nari Khan.
Amartya Rao.
I'm serving time for narcotics.
And you?
For daring.
Beat him!
Kill him!
Hey...
Stay back!
Back.
Gaitonde, that's enough!
Gaitonde!
Look at the sun!
From now it'll
rise only for me.
Your story's over,
and my saga begins!
Amartya Rao, you've been given bail.
Amartya.
When faced with obstacles,
most collapse...
... and some rise up.
It's time for you to rise.
Here.
You'll need this.
Goodbye.
Father.
Is everything alright, son?
I was worried about you.
Come on, uncle.
You didn't give birth to a son...
You gave birth to a legend.
- How is Arjun?
- He's doing well...
... in the VIP ward.
Who put him there?
The same guy who bailed you out!
Bhau.
He wants to meet you.
He's sent a car.
Ask.
Bhau, rumours are
that you had a hand...
... in the Behram Baug riots last week?
You got it wrong.
Not just a hand,
I had my leg in there too.
It was a kick on their asses.
I called him up and told him...
to handle the situation.
Otherwise, I'd have to handle it.
- Did I tell you or not?
- You did, Bhau.
And that's what I did.
My boys struck them
in their own territory.
But innocent lives
were also lost in the clash.
When a shot is fired the bullet
is blind to caste or creed.
So do you take
responsibility for the riots?
I only take responsibility
for keeping my city clean.
But people say that
you're spreading terror.
- They are scared of you.
- That's good.
They should be scared!
Right?
- But Bhau, Democracy...
- This is my Democracy!
- And how do you justify it?
- I don't have to.
- Patil.
- Sir...
- The interview is over.
- Yes, sir.
See you.
Patil.
All okay?
Bhau, this is Amartya.
Sit.
So... you want to be a gangster?
I'm here because
I was trying to be a brother.
But looking at your splendor...
... I think it's better to be You.
Patience. Patience.
Your time will come.
Everyone's time comes.
But I'll have my era.
Not without my support.
When I beat up Gaitonde's
boys in the market...
... I was alone.
When I fought all day in jail...
... I was still alone.
Why would I need you now?
You will.
A soldier can be smart...
... but he needs an army to win wars,
which I have.
I've seen your brawn,
now I want to see your brain.
Gaitonde is your problem.
Not mine, he's your problem.
Meet me after a week.
When you have a
solution to the problem!
- Grandpa...
- Here comes my child.
Your vacation is over already…
I always lose track
of your holidays.
Focus on your studies. Okay.
Go on.
Which school does he go to?
I'll study properly in Bombay.
And won't get into any trouble.
This is not a punishment.
This is for your own good.
This is your home now...
... away from the filth of Bombay.
Even during your vacations,
you won't come to Bombay.
I'll come here instead.
Understood.
Can't do it.
You'll have to do it.
Now hurry up, or you'll be late.
Take care.
What's wrong?
Aren't you happy?
I am.
Then why do you have
tears in your eyes?
I am all alone now.
Alone, huh?
What happened?
Take care of him.
He's all alone now.
What?
Amar, shall we start planning?
Think again.
Once we get in, there's no way out.
It's a one-way ticket.
He got in the day
he chopped Poytya's hand.
After all that's happened,
Gaitonde won't backdown.
Meaning?
Meaning we'll have to go after him.
We're only a dozen
while he has an army.
So what?
Even we'll have an army.
I'll go to our neighborhood...
... and gather the boys.
But still Amar, it's dangerous.
Danger only gets worse if you don't face it.
So now?
I have a solution.
The boat over there.
You want to finish Gaitonde...
... then hit him where it hurts.
How?
By making your own territory...
... by chasing him
out of his.
Only if your guts are greater
than your strength can you rule this city.
Do you have the guts?
It's all we have.
What do we have to do?
First things first,
you need to get a van.
Not from Dadar.
Someplace far.
Vasai. Virar.
Or even Panvel.
After that, you need to abduct this man.
Gaitonde's right hand.
Listen you idiot...
Answer our questions if
you know what's best for you.
Otherwise, your head will be sitting over
there talking to the rest of your body.
Understood.
Now... where does Gaitonde
store his weapons?
Tell me.
Did you hear?
Can you hear now?
Start talking.
I won't ask again.
I'll tell you. I'll talk.
There are three places.
Mazgaon Jetty.
Gokhle Garage. And...
Oh, God.
...Dadar Mill.
Now beat him.
But I told you everything.
Exactly.
I don't like traitors.
Make sure he doesn't
wake up for three days.
No.
Ahire.
Singhya...
In these guns is your
strength and your protection.
Fire.
But who do we shoot at?
What's the hell?
It's empty.
I wanted to see whose
hand shivers while firing a gun.
Anna, even his feet
are shivering. Look.
From here... straight.
- We want a leader like...
- Vishal Patil.
- Glory to...
- Jan Seva Party!
- We want a leader like...
- Vishal Patil.
What is this?
Go back.
This is Gaitonde's area.
Jan Seva's rally.
And you want us to go back.
I don't care whose rally this is.
And this is my area now.
Are you trying to scare us with a gun?
I carry a gun because I like to.
To scare the likes of you,
my name is enough
Rao...
Amartya Rao.
This is your sacred boundary.
When a goddess crossed it,
it led to a battle.
If you do, it'll lead to a War!
Let's go.
Salutations Bhau.
Your back?
Sit.
You gave me a week.
And you came back in 5-days.
Isn't that what you want to say?
Is your brother doing
well at the boarding school?
He's doing great.
Thank you.
You see...
When you have nothing to lose...
... you have the entire world to conquer.
I'll do that too, Bhau.
Just need your blessings.
From today
Mumbai city is yours.
Go rule.
Nari bhai,
you've been granted bail.
Unbelievable.
I knew you will come back.
From today Nari Khan
will be known by another name.
The Brother's brother.
What's this for?
For the next meeting!
Don't be scared, Gaitonde.
If he can come this far,
he can also kill you.
- He's come to talk.
- Tell me.
If you hadn't screwed up,
I'd be still looked upon as a clean man.
I don't understand...
Are you complaining or are you thanking me.
Complaints are for family,
which you're not.
And I thank only the lord above.
I came here to tell you Gaitonde...
... that from Dadar to Byculla
is now my area.
Your area...
fine.
I've spent 23-years
in this business.
The only thing I learnt
in these last 23-years is...
... that nothing is permanent here.
Nothing.
Understood.
Yesterday it was mine,
today it's yours...
...and tomorrow it'll be someone else's.
Until then... long live Mumbai.
Enjoy.
I won't enjoy... I'll rule!
"Glory to Lord Ganesha..."
"Ganesha... Ganesha... Ganesha..."
"Your devotee has arrived, o Lord."
"You're his saviour, o Ganesha."
"He's come with folded
hands and an overwhelmed heart..."
"... only you dwell in it, o Ganesha."
"Glory to Lord Ganesha..."
"Glory to the Benevolent Lord."
"Your devotee has arrived, o Lord."
"You're his saviour, o Ganesha."
"He's come with folded
hands and an overwhelmed heart..."
"... only you dwell in it, o Ganesha."
"Those who pray to you,
know your strength."
"You desecrate all our worries."
"Beat the drums aloud..."
"... here comes Lord Ganesha."
"Let your heart beat aloud."
"Beat the drums aloud..."
"... here comes Lord Ganesha."
"Let your heart beat aloud."
"The benevolent one,
the generous one..."
"The protector of good...
destroyer of evil."
"The wise one..."
"Lord Ganesha..."
"Destroyer of all sorrows,
provider of happiness."
"Lord Ganesha..."
"Ganesha... Ganesha... Ganesha..."
"Glory to Lord Ganesha..."
Thanks.
So... dad, you were saying?
I didn't send you to Harvard...
so you could come back
and try to convince me...
... that the mill your
grandfather built from scratch
should be sold.
Don't scream,
father-in-law.
It's not good for
your blood pressure.
Look, dad, even if your 5600 workers
work for a lifetime...
... they won't earn for you what I can...
... with this single deal.
And our mill's land, which is on lease...
And was impossible to sell earlier...
... can now be sold.
The Ministry has changed
its laws to make it possible.
Laws have been changed
because you bribed the ministers
with the same greed.
Everyone wants a piece
of this city to make money.
So what's wrong with that?
Every person wants
to earn money, dad.
Listen, dad.
My grandfather built this
mill from scratch.
Why?
To make money right?
To do business.
Not for charity.
And dad, the past and
the future are both called tenses.
We have to decide which
tense we want to live in.
I don't know about your future...
... but this mill is not for sale...
... not as long as I'm alive.
Fuck.
Arjun, here are your shirts...
What's wrong with you?
Why the long face?
I don't want to go to London.
You've been living
alone for 8-years,
... never even wrote a letter.
And suddenly you're
getting emotional about
leaving your brother
and me.
Oh I see... these feelings
are for someone else.
So who is she?
What does she do?
Her name is Neelam.
We used to study together.
So what's the problem.
What if she marries
someone else after I leave?
Who will get her married?
Her father.
Have you seen your brother?
He's the Godfather.
I'll handle it.
Does she have a passport?
Yes, she does.
But passport...
She'll need it for her London visa.
Didn't she tell you?
What, dear?
No, she did tell me...
First the wedding,
and then London...
... for Arjun to finish
his higher studies.
But why now?
Why not?
Don't worry.
Just tell us the venue.
We'll make all the arrangements.
You see, no one says no to him.
No one...
He likes oats, cereals,
bread and butter for breakfast.
He loves meat.
But please stay away
from beef and pork.
And it's cold there, Make sure he
wears a jacket at all times.
Otherwise, if Arjun sneezes there...
... his brother will catch a cold here.
Brother, this is a one-way ticket.
Yes, because I don't want
you to come back to this city.
Just like in school...
... Even when you have vacations,
I'll come and see you there.
It's okay.
Let's go.
He's all alone again.
Why will he be alone?
You guys are there no for him.
Let's go.
Your fathers dead...
... and these mill
workers are feeling orphaned.
Since they are orphaned,
Make them homeless too.
20,000 for vacating every
worker out of their home!
20,000!
What about the worker's wife,
children, mother, father, uncle?
Do I drag them out for free?
What do you mean?
Meaning, according to my
calculations, with this deal...
... you stand to make
a profit of 8 billion.
And you're offering me 90 million.
Look here.
What do I look like to you?
Loose change is for beggars,
not partners.
I want 15%
- Done.
- Done! Done! Done!
Great.
The Portuguese named
this city Bom Bahia...
And you know what...
They gave it as a wedding
gift to the British.
They thought it was their father's property.
And the British changed
its name to Bombay.
But now enough.
Our city won't be known by a name...
... given by the British!
This city belongs
to our Goddess Mumba Devi.
She's our mother.
This city will no longer
be known as Bombay...
... but as Mumbai!
What will it be called?
Mumbai!
- What will it be called?
- Mumbai!
What will this city be called?
Mumbai! Mumbai! Mumbai!
Greetings, Bhau.
It's heavy.
But do you know what
is heavier than a gun?
Money.
With money,
one can buy as many of these.
Khaitaan has joined hands with Gaitonde.
Now... after the mill deal,
Khaitaan won't have
any shortage of money...
... and Gaitonde of guns.
Clip Khaitaan's wings and Gaitonde
will come crashing to the ground.
If you want to move ahead in life,
then always remember two things.
Who you want and what he wants!
I want the votes
of those mill workers...
... and they want their rights.
And I want what you want.
Don't worry.
Amartya... you're my pride.
Don't ever let it down.
Never.
You won't win this race.
We'll only know after the race ends.
Any deal that gives you Gaitonde's friendship...
... along with Amartya Rao's enmity...
... can never be very profitable.
I don't need you to
teach me profit and loss.
I went to Harvard
University for that.
But looks like you didn't learn anything.
It's not too late yet.
Mend your ways.
It's already too late, Amartya Rao.
The race has already begun
and the bet has been placed.
And my bet is on Gaitonde.
And one doesn't change
bets in the middle of the race.
In a race of horses,
you've bet on a mule.
Your car is bulletproof...
Your not.
Come on!
- Where to?
- To meet Gaitonde.
No cars allowed beyond this point!
What is this?
Enough!
What's wrong?
I don't want to
do business with you.
What's wrong with you?
Why so angry?
I don't want to risk
my life just to make money.
But who is going to kill you?
Amartya Rao.
Inspite of having you on my side he dared
to publicly threaten me at the racecourse.
He might even kill me.
24-hours.
You have only 24-hours
or else the deal's cancelled.
Amar has thrown a stone...
... I'll reply with a flower.
But the flower will be on his grave.
Look...
Arjun!
Here.
So... you've grown even bigger and taller.
Stop it, brother.
How much bigger will I get now?
But Arjun,
you shouldn't have come back.
- But...
- It's his brother's birthday.
How could he not come?
Okay. Come. Let's go.
Baba... Jagannath?
Don't be afraid.
Look behind.
- Neelam!
- Arjun!
Let's go. Come on.
Hurry up!
You shouldn't have come back.
I...
This is why I kept
you away for 10-years.
And now you show up
to stick your head into the fire.
Have you lost your mind!
But brother, I only wanted
to give you a surprise.
They shot at you, Arjun!
You could've lost your life!
They came to kill you!
Is this how you want to surprise me?
But nothing happened.
I won't do it again.
Please talk to him.
Amar...
I am not a kid anymore.
Hey...
You'll always be a kid for me.
Understood!
They shouldn't have attacked Arjun.
I'm done talking.
It's time to put an end to this story.
Drive faster.
What are you doing?
Turn it around.
Quickly.
Turn the car around!
Move, move fast.
By attacking my brother.
You turned this race
track into a jungle
And in the jungle,
only the fittest survive.
I warned you...
Your car is bulletproof...
Not you.
It's a temple.
No guns!
I think you're in a
hurry to meet your Creator.
I just came to tell you Gaitonde...
... whenever you lay
a finger on my brother,
your men will either lose an arm...
... or a head.
As for meeting with the Creator...
I've already sent,
your partner Khaitaan, to meet his.
Look at these stairs, Gaitonde.
We're both standing
in the same place.
Except for one difference...
You're going down,
and I am going up.
Commissioner!
Six hours ago, Amartya Rao...
... murdered a reputed
industrialist on the streets.
An industrialist who was
going to change the face of Bombay...
... and put it on the map of the world.
My husband. Sunil Khaitaan.
I lost a husband,
But the real loss is of Bombay city.
100 million!
100 million to the officer who puts
a bullet in Amartya Rao's head!
What do you think, Sir?
Will Amartya die?
The question is not
whether Amartya will die?
The question is what will I
do with a 100 million.
Don't challenge our pride.
If you awaken a sleeping tiger...
... he will tear you apart.
Don't mess with my family.
If you mess with us,
We will hit back.
What did I say?
If you mess with us,
We will hit back.
Hit back! Hit back!
If anyone dares to takes your rights...
... he'll be lying on the
streets covered in his own blood.
I clearly told the government...
... If you have your guy in Dubai,
I have mine in Dadar.
My brothers,
for the blessings of Chhatrapati...
... and the pride of our people,
you must vote for Chhtrapati's
army in the coming elections...
- Long live...
- Marathi Unity!
Long live...
Come. I need to hear
other slogans from you.
Everyone has a favorite
spot which changes with time.
As a kid the park near my house
was my favorite.
When in school it was the last row in class.
In College it was the canteen.
When I got a girlfriend
it was the corner seats of the theatre.
And once I wore
this Police uniform...
... and became an
encounter specialist...
... this has been my favorite spot.
I've got something to show you.
Look.
I brought them all here.
Don't worry,
I'll give you a chance to run too.
Run!
No, sir.
I don't want to go anywhere.
Scared.
Ask me whatever you want.
I'll tell you everything.
You will!
A dog always pees in the same place.
Chandu, Jadhav, Mahesh, Gotya,
and Mangu... Where do they go?
Tell me.
Speak up.
The food was too
spicy today, Babban.
Next time I won't eat here.
See you.
Hey, Chandu.
Will you get in or run?
Where do you think you're going?
You don't even give me a look now.
You won't screw anyone today,
Jadhav.
It's your turn to get screwed today.
First strike is mine, Gotya.
So what's on the menu today?
Fish curry, crab, and fish fry.
And a police bullet for dessert.
Come out, Ganpat.
Else the car will need to
be washed from the inside as well.
Chandu in front
of the roadside stall.
Jadhav in a whore house.
And Gotya... he was playing carrom
in the neighbourhood.
He shot him there.
Manku in the hermitage...
... and that Mahesh was
visiting his mistress.
And he shot him there.
I've known Manku for so long.
Even I didn't know
he had a mistress.
You didn't know, but someone did.
Jadhav, Chandu, Gotya, Manku...
About everyone.
When you plan to steal from a house
... The servant is the first guy
you need on your side.
There's an informer among us.
Who could it be?
The one who is not here.
Sadashiv.
Arjun, what are you saying?
Sada?
Never. It's not possible.
He's our childhood friend.
He's a buddy.
The thing about betrayal is...
... it's always someone
special who does it.
Call Sadashiv and tell
him to meet me at Five Gardens.
What?
What if he sends cops there?
That's what I've got to see.
Wait.
Crime Branch head office.
The place is swarming
with cops, sir.
I guess you're laying the
bait for a big player.
Hitting a boundary on a small field
doesn't make the player big.
He won't last too long.
I guess luck was on his side today.
He survived.
He'll have to be lucky
every time to get away from me.
But I'll have to be
lucky only once to kill him.
Luck is like a car's gear, sir.
Shift it at the right time and
it changes the pace of your life.
Nice punch line.
Did you come to Bombay
to become an actor?
You're very clever, sir.
Got me in the first meeting.
- How much?
- Let it be, sir.
I can't take money from you.
I am not that kind of cop.
I knew that right away.
But I don't often get
a chance to help the Law.
Just shake hands Sir.
Whenever luck is on your side,
and you get that player...
... I'll proudly say that
I shook hands with death.
- Everything alright?
- No.
I called you so many times, Amar.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I am okay.
I couldn't stop worrying about you.
Couldn't focus on anything.
I don't answer your calls only
when death is in front me.
Today it was sitting on the backseat.
Come.
So Sadashiv sold us out.
He didn't sell out.
He got scared.
My information was right, sir.
Amar was supposed
to come to Five Gardens.
He himself told me.
Then why didn't he show up?
There can only be one reason.
He knows that it's me.
He won't spare me now.
He won't spare you, that's why we're
taking you to your hometown.
Go there and lead a quiet life.
Where are you going?
There are no office rooms on a moving train
We're going to the bathroom.
You broke our trust for money,
Sadashiv.
Not for money.
In exchange for my life!
If I hadn't told that inspector
everything, he would've shot me.
That would've been better.
You would've died as a loyal friend.
Now you'll die a traitor.
Why, Sada?
Baba, you're my brother.
Forgive me.
I was scared.
How many creams rolls
was it this time?
I had no guts.
And I... was cornered.
Here.
What's the second packet for?
For taking a bullet!
You'll shot Sadashiv in broad daylight!
Fired at cops!
How did you dare help Arjun
without my permission?
He thought my life
was a bigger priority.
Baba knows that I would've
killed Sadashiv anyway.
Who gave you the
right to kill Sadashiv?
I picked up a gun,
so you never have to!
I shed blood but never
let a drop fall on you.
And you want to kill people.
I will.
I killed just one today.
Tomorrow there may be a dozen against you!
I'll kill all of them.
You did everything
you could for me, brother!
Now it's my turn.
You're not the only one
that gets to be a good brother.
You did more than you could, Amar.
Now destiny too has to play it's part.
Greetings, Bhau.
- Greetings.
Amar...
I told you to scare Khaitaan,
not kill him.
You fired shots here...
... And they were heard all the way in Delhi.
I can understand why
you killed Sadashiv.
He was an informer.
But shooting those cops?
They were paid to take the bullets.
Now they'll get a medal,
instead of an inquiry.
Get him a chair.
The silence in the jungle
announces the lion's presence.
And people don't wander
into the jungle out of fear.
But when the lion comes to the
city to hunt...
... the entire city
unites to kill him.
What do you want me to do?
Leave the city.
Even the country.
If the chief runs away
then what about his army?
A dead chief is
no good for the army.
If the army exists,
so will the chief.
Let Arjun lead the
army for a few days.
Vijay.
Even his brother has joined the gang now.
What's your plan?
In the Mahabharat Arjun shot the arrow
into the bird's eye.
I am going to aim
for Arjun's eye instead.
He'll lead us to Amartya.
And then?
Then I'll get my shot, sir.
Welcome, sir.
Welcome.
Come, sit.
So glad you could make it, Sir.
You couldn't have managed even a small
affair on a constable's salary...
... but look at this.
This is enough to pay for
the whole department's daughters weddings.
Sir, meet my wife and daughter.
- Hello.
Sir, please bless my child.
Take his blessings.
God bless you.
Your father's taken a lot of trouble
for the sake of your happiness... .
... and he'll keep doing it.
- Sir, have some sweets.
- Sir...
I don't eat sweets.
But give him.
He loves to eat.
Right?
Please...
Thank you.
Open your mouth.
Huh?
Open your mouth, Samant.
You will open your mouth.
Now...
... open your mouth wide and tell me...
... who killed Sadashiv?
And how much did you
get paid for it?
Otherwise, I'll shove the wedding
trumpet up so far...
... that you'll be
breathing through it.
It was a mistake, Sir. Forgive me.
Name!
Arjun Rao.
Savarkar. Encounter Specialist.
He's come to talk.
Arjun, be careful.
The Police always comes unannounced.
Bad news and bad times
also come unannounced.
Even Sadashiv's death
came unannounced.
Why did you cross my path?
Not just your path,
I've crossed your stars.
The government gave you
a uniform, a gun...
... and God gave you fingers.
Doesn't mean you
finger everyone?
You shot our boys on the streets,
the whore house, the garage...
But you shot them all
in the back.
Shoot me from the front.
I won't turn my back.
I don't need a gun to put you down.
For that the law is enough.
Your educated, right?
Read this.
And read it carefully.
Call up your brother and tell
him that you're done.
Because Savarkar's
charged you with TADA.
See you in court.
And yes...
... if you have a death wish,
then don't come to the court.
Because as soon as the
court declares you an absconder...
... I'll gun you down
in the middle of the street.
And not in the back
I'll shoot you in the chest.
Savarkar is cunning.
He's put Arjun in a complicated situation
by charging him with TADA.
He knows there's no bail in TADA.
If Arjun doesn't
show up in the court,
they will declare him an absconder.
We're stuck between the devil
and the deep blue sea.
Where else will Arjun
go after getting arrested?
Arthur Road Jail.
And Arthur Road Jail is
more of Gaitonde's fortress.
Where he can easily
kill Arjun.
Who is the judge of the TADA court?
Justice Malkani.
Malkani...
But if the judge is on Bhau's payroll,
then what are we afraid of?
Even if the judge
is on Bhau's payroll...
... Arjun will still have
to go to court for bail.
Where he will be attacked.
Arjun!
- Mrs. Rao.
- Doctor...
The vitals are good.
The bullet has hit on
the spinal thoracic vertebra.
His nerves are damaged.
Meaning?
- He won't be able to walk.
- What?
He's paralyzed!
He used to sell vegetables earlier...
... now he'll be a
vegetable all his life.
Amartya must be really sad today...
... he must be wishing why
didn't the bullet kill him.
Now the snake will
come out of his burrow.
Sir...
Mhatre, I want cops on all
entry and exit points.
Sir.
- Hello.
- Seema.
Greetings, Bhau.
God bless you, Seema.
- Where is Amar?
- He isn't here.
Tell him to stay away from Mumbai.
After what happened with Arjun,
no one can stop him.
Look, Seema, Amar's enemies
are waiting for this opportunity.
He knows, Bhau.
And even I know he'll be
loyal to every relationship...
... as a brother and as a foe!
Tell him these are Bhau's orders.
His life vests in you, Bhau...
But for his brother...
He can give up his life.
What's going on?
A large mob has barged
inside and they're protesting.
They claim that a child died
because of a doctor's negligence.
Are all the officers in place?
Some are posted outside
Arjun's room, sir.
The rest are helping
in controlling the crowd.
It's a setup.
This mob is here to distract us.
Are you in pain?
Not much.
Everything will be fine.
I left Seema back in London.
They have the best doctors.
Don't be scared.
With you brother fear is the only
thing I never learned.
And I won't now.
Does fate test everyone...
... or does it have
a grudge with me only?
The younger brother who
can't walk manages to escape.
And the older brother is missing.
And no one knows where they are.
What is this nonsense?
Are we a joke, Vijay?
- We need results.
- Sir.
Yes, Seema.
Arjun's with me at Bhau's farmhouse.
We're safe here.
Fine, we'll talk later.
Everything's ready.
We'll take down that bloody
Gaitonde on his own turf.
Not yet.
We must get Arjun out first.
And for that,
I must meet with Nari Khan.
- I'll fix it.
- Ok.
Amar, until the Khaitaan murder
case isn't shut...
... the Police won't
stop chasing you.
I know.
And I also know there's
no way out of here.
- There is a way.
- What?
If one of us confesses
to killing Khaitaan...
... then the Police
will stop chasing you.
Who will do that?
- Me.
- Have you lost your mind, Jaggan?
No one put a gun to our head
to come into this line of work.
We entered this line on our own.
Knowing fully well where it ends.
And when you're in trouble...
... how can I rest easy?
Take care.
Sit.
Sir, are you serious?
Archenemies often
keep a tab on each other.
Prepare to go to Gaitonde Chawl.
Come on.
What are you doing?
We're going to Gaitonde Chawl,
right?
We can't go there in our uniforms.
The mob there...
I mean it's less dangerous
in plain clothes.
Danger?
We're cops.
What can be more dangerous
than our uniforms?
After four years of training...
... we stood under the scorching sun
in this uniform and took an oath.
Not so we can take it off for
cheap criminals like Gaitonde.
Why do you carry these stars
on your shoulders then?
Take them off!
If we can proudly pin
a medal on this uniform...
... then we can also
take a bullet on it.
Sir, we're ready.
Cops are coming!
Hide the guns!
Come on. Quickly.
Hurry up.
Gather everything around.
Run! Run!
Tell that rat to
come out of his hole.
If I can come till here...
... I can also put
a bullet in his head.
Don't worry,
if I wanted to kill you...
... you'd already be dead by now.
There's still time for you
to meet your maker Gaitonde.
So what do you want?
Amartya Rao.
Amartya...
He's in my pocket.
Put your hand in
and take him out.
How can I give you Amartya?
You will...
Because people like you keep
more tabs about your enemies.
Meaning... the enemy of my enemy...
is my friend?
No.
We can never be friends.
But if you give me Amartya...
... then I might drop the
idea of becoming your enemy.
I won't count to three.
In fact, I won't count at all.
Have you lost your mind?
Put it down.
Put it down. Put it down.
- What if it fires?
- It will...
If you don't start talking.
Nari Khan.
Amartya's old friend.
They are always together.
He's changed his appearance now.
But he's still got
an evil mind.
Where is Nari Khan?
Keep a lookout on the
Daman-Gujarat border.
There's an Amazon bar out there.
Nari Khan goes there often.
He does all his narcotics
deals over there.
Hopefully you may find Amartya there.
Determination drives me, not hope.
"Yo Yo Honey Singh."
"Make some... Make some..."
"No one's ever escaped my sight."
"I can make you dance into the night."
"Keep dancing till
the sun comes up..."
"... and your feet start to swell up."
"I am the cure to your pain..."
"... I will make you forget your bane."
"My business is not straight..."
"... Chaos is what I create."
"That's why..."
"Make some... Make some..."
"Noise!"
"Rock it... Rock it."
"The floor."
"Make some... Make some..."
"Rock it... Rock it."
"The floor."
"I'll spare no one in this party..."
"... break your legs if you do not party."
"Whether I grow bottles on trees..."
"... or make everyone sway to my beats."
"Breathe free... don't choke to death."
"Roll some grass little by little."
"If you don't trust
the dope you receive..."
"... use it first
And then believe."
"Make some... Make some..."
"Noise!"
"Rock it... Rock it."
"The floor."
"Make some... Make some..."
"Rock it... Rock it."
"The floor."
"Pick up the booze..."
"... let your body loose."
"And till the lights fuse..."
"... I'll keep loving you
till you drop."
"I won't misuse you,
but make you pop."
"Don't be shy, come closer."
"Take me in your arms...
"... let the fun begin."
"Every day you'll say..."
"Make some... Make some..."
"Noise!"
"Rock it... Rock it."
"The floor."
"Make some... Make some..."
"Yo Yo Honey Singh."
"Homie..."
"From Delhi..."
"Make some... Make some..."
Amartya.
Amartya, didn't you hear me?
Are you talking to me?
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
And I think you just gave
away your fake disguise.
By bowing your head in front of a temple.
You changed you looks,
but not your habits.
Some habits are hard to quit...
... like the habit to stay alive.
Don't worry, I'll make
you quit that soon.
When it's time to do or die...
... then one prepares.
And I am always prepared.
I was even prepared when
you were sitting behind me.
I'm prepared now
when you are in front of me.
Doesn't matter how hard you try...
... but you can't
get this player out.
As I said, to escape my bullet
you'll have to be lucky at all times...
... but I'll have
to be lucky just once.
Then let's see whether
luck smiles on you...
... or I still have a chance left.
Hello.
Hi. Come, sit.
This is Joshi.
He is in Narcotics.
Joshi, tell him.
Tell him everything.
Savarkar and I took our
Police training together.
I've known him for a long time.
So?
We were youth leaders in Bhau's party.
Every year dozens of
boys from Bhau's party...
join the Police force...
... and some of us make it
to very senior postings.
But not without Bhau's approval.
Promotions, departments, transfers.
Bhau decides everything.
Meaning Bhau has his own
force within the Police force.
So, senior officers like you and
Savarkar still take orders from Bhau?
We only take orders from Bhau.
Leave alone an encounter
We don't even file a report without his orders.
You work for Bhau.
Savarkar also works for Bhau.
Then why is he after you?
That's a question
Bhau will have to answer.
What's the emergency...
That you had to call me here, Amar?
Your dog came to bite me,
but could only manage to bark.
Savarkar was in your party
before joining the Police force.
So what?
He's gets his salary from the government...
... but orders from you.
Amar, for a guy who earns 7000 a month...
... a 100 million
is a lot of money.
Forget loyalty, people sell their souls
For that kind of money.
You need to focus on getting
your brother out of here.
Keeping Vijay out of your way
is my guarantee.
So long, Bhau.
See you.
Greetings, Bhau.
Viju, you know Amartya works for me right?
And still you're going after him.
At times one has
to do his duty too, Bhau.
Never forget one thing Viju,
I put you where you are.
People like you uphold the law for me...
... and people like Amartya
break the law for me.
in your own capacity
you both work for me.
You are two sides
of the same coin.
And when the time
comes to flip the coin...
... I decide who wins and who loses.
Okay Bhau on your orders...
I'll get out of Amartya's way.
Good.
But if you get out of his way
then who will get him out of the way?
I'll come back as
soon as Arjun is settled.
We'll handle everything.
No one's going to last against us.
I know.
Always told your father
He didn't give birth to a son...
He gave birth to a legend.
You have to be careful from now on.
We've got no one on our side, Baba.
Not even Bhau.
Our strength is no longer above us...
... it's within us.
Don't worry, I'll handle things.
Take care.
What do you think, brother?
Does fate write our story,
or do we?
Fate takes control
only when we let it.
Did I decide this for myself?
It was destined, it happened.
I was writing your destiny.
And everything was
fine until I was doing it.
Yes, Seema?
Are you okay, Amar?
I am on the airstrip.
Arjun's with me.
I was worried.
When are you not worried?
Just wasn't getting a good feeling.
We'll leave as soon
as the plane arrives.
Remember Amar,
if anything happens to you...
... then there will be
no one to look after me.
I know.
The planes' here.
I'll call you as soon as we board.
Tower, jeep on the runway.
Turning around.
Hey... what's going on?
There is a jeep on the runway, sir.
The plane will crash.
Land the bloody plane.
I said land the bloody plane.
Alright.
- Are you alright?
- I am alright.
But how did the inspector
find out we were here?
Come.
Start the engine.
Brother!
Go!
Mumbai city is yours.
Go rule.
Yes, Bhau.
Thank you.